[muffled punch thrown]
[audience yelling]
-[shouts] Let's go!
-Come on!
[punch thrown]
-[man 2] Let's move!
Get him!
-[grunts]
[kick thrown]
[audience yelling]
-That's it, man!
-Go, go, go, go!
-Come on! Come on!
[audience whoops]
[spits]
[audience cheering and whooping]
[punch thrown]
[blood sputters]
[high-pitched ringing]
[audience boos]
[heartbeat pulsating]
-[man 4] Stand up, you sucker!
-[grunting] Come on!
[grunts]
[blows land]
[audience yelling]
[body thuds]
[grunts, strains]
[whistles]
[audience cheering]
-Let's go!
-[yelling] Ahh!
[gun cocks]
[panting]
[gunshot]
[mysterious music]
[electric guitar melody plays]
-[over radio] [indistinct]
[vehicle approaching]
[music fades]
-[Bender] Atlas King!
-Bender.
Didn't think
I'd be seeing you again.
-Wish it were under better
circumstances, brother.
-So tell me what happened
with Dutch.
You sure there
was no foul play?
-It was suicide.
The fight venue's
been losing money.
He's in a lot of debt.
-Who found him?
-Tommy.
Kid wouldn't let anybody
near his father.
Penelope finally talked
some sense into him.
-You still with Penny?
-Some things last, my friend.
Come on.
She'll be happy to see you.
[melancholic music]
-I thought I'd see you
one last time, my friend.
[sighs]
[footsteps approaching]
-Hey, Atlas.
-Good to see you, Penny.
I came back as soon as I heard.
-Demons he was fighting
finally got the better of him.
We have a room made up for you.
You're not staying
in some hotel across town.
-I'm only staying
for the funeral.
-No. It's not that easy.
You don't get to just
walk out on us again.
-Come on, Penny.
That wasn't my choice,
and you know it.
Dutch saved my life
by ordering me to leave town.
Also stopped the heat
coming down on everyone else.
-And look where it got him.
-Penelope, just let it go.
-[sighs]
Please stay out of this.
My father could have used
your help these last few years.
If he'd had you with him,
he would still be here.
-All he had to do
was reach out,
and I would have come back.
-Well, he's reached out now,
hasn't he?
With Dutch gone,
there's blood in the water.
Men are already feeding
on scraps,
and the vulture in the city
is circling,
waiting to take what's left
of his territory.
Tommy's caught in the middle.
If somebody
doesn't pull him out,
he's going to end up
just like our old man.
Dutch brought you the fuck home
for a reason.
He needed Atlas King,
the fucking Mad Dog,
[chuckles] to come back
and clean up this shit up.
So don't you tell me
that you are just here
for the funeral!
Is that the man you are?
[lips smack]
I'm gonna go check
on the guests,
or I'll never hear
the end of it.
-[sighs]
[taps coffin]
[exhales]
I see why you're still
with her.
Where's Tommy?
-He's down at the docks.
-Let's go get him.
[suspenseful music]
[audience clamoring]
[locker clangs]
-[grunts]
Come on!
[grunts]
[punches thrown]
[audience clamoring]
[grunts]
Get him, Tommy!
[punches thrown]
-[man] You fucking [indistinct]?
-Go! Get the motherfucker!
-[grunts]
[punches thrown]
[straining]
[body thumps]
[punches thrown]
-[panting]
-[grunting]
[locker clangs]
-Yeah!
-Come on, yeah!
[audience clamoring]
That's it! Yeah!
-What the fuck
is Tommy doing,
fighting my guy tonight?
I didn't sanction this.
Ain't that nigga supposed
to be burying his father?
-He's a fucking wild man.
He's just letting off steam.
-[grunting]
[punches thrown]
-Get him!
-Let's go, hey!
-Chill your ass out.
-Come on!
Fuck off, fucker!
[straining] Let's go!
-[Tommy grunting]
-Everybody get out.
[gun clicks]
Everybody get the fuck out!
-[man 3] Let's go!
-[Tommy strains]
-[soft cackle]
Stopped by the funeral
to pay my respects,
and they said you
weren't around, so...
-No matter how much
my father paid,
you never let him get out
from under it.
-Oh, don't try laying
your father's death at my feet.
-You may not have pulled
the trigger,
but you handed him the gun.
-Now let me ask you this.
Dutch think
all would be forgiven
once he took
the cowardly way out?
I'm just--
-[grunting]
[smacks]
-[Mac] Easy there, doggie.
Easy.
-[chuckling]
He owed me 200 grand,
plus the vig.
And that meter's been running
a awful long time, cuz.
-[panting]
-Hmm. So here's what's up.
Since he couldn't pay me,
you, you're a fighter,
you aint no businessman.
You gonna sign
over the fight venue to me,
and I'll let you bury
your father.
-First chance I get,
I'm gonna fucking kill you.
So you might as well
pull that trigger.
-Well you heard the man.
Shoot this motherfucker.
[gun clicks]
[tense music]
[gun cocks]
-[Atlas King] Looks like
we're late for the party.
Lower the fucking piece
and step the fuck back,
you cunt!
-Or we can all go together.
-[straining]
-Good to see you, kid.
-Weren't you supposed
to have run off somewhere
in the world where nobody
gives a shit about?
-Ten years is a long time, Clay.
-Well, rules is rules, cuz.
You are off limits
in this city, Atlas.
And now that Dutch is gone,
ain't got nobody
to protect your ass.
-I ran the fight venue
with Dutch.
We were 50/50 on it.
So if there's a debt,
then it's on me too.
So let's make a deal.
We're gonna end it right here,
right now.
-[chuckles]
You always had a loud bark.
And look where that got
your ass.
-Which one should I shoot first,
boss?
-[chuckles]
Pick one of these motherfuckers!
I've waited ten years
to get my hands on your ass.
I can wait a little longer.
You kick in fifty grand a month
for the next six months.
Then after that,
sixty percent
of the fight venue is mine.
-He'll never keep his end of it.
-Yeah, but then his name
doesn't mean shit in this town.
Ain't that right, Clay?
-Hmm. Till the debt is paid,
you can do business
in this town.
And after that,
you and I are gonna do
a little dance, homeboy.
Bury your patriarch.
Mourn him.
From now on, you work for me.
Hear me?
-I'm gonna fuckin' kill him.
-Emerson is too powerful
to take on alone.
Everyone is on his payroll.
You go after him,
the whole city's gonna
come down on you.
-You've been gone ten years,
and now you're gonna come back
and make deals for the family?
-[Bender] Whoa, come on, Tommy.
Show the guy some respect.
There's a reason your dad
always trusted him.
-Fuck this!
-[Bender] Tommy!
-Ah. He's a hothead.
Just like Dutch was.
[train humming]
[low, foreboding music]
[metal door opens]
[metal door closes]
[keys jingling]
[rope squeaks]
[sentimental music]
[sentimental music continues]
[panting]
Ahh!
[taps on metal pole]
[door opens]
[paper rustling]
[glass bottle clinks]
[liquor pouring]
[sighs]
This one's for you, Dutch.
[satisfied pant]
[knock on door]
-Olivia.
It's good to see you.
-Back only a day and already
stirring the hornet's nest.
Gonna stick around this time?
This how you greet
your old friends?
-I was gonna call you,
once I got a few things sorted.
-Whatever you've gotten yourself
into with Clay,
it won't go the way you hope.
-So you work for Emerson now?
-Things have changed
since you left.
I don't work for anyone.
I broker deals
and introduce people
with common interests.
-Did he send you to see me?
-He has a new fighter
he wants to show off next week.
Said to make sure
you promote the fight,
he'll bring some guests.
-All right.
Anything else?
-Fifty grand every month
comes to me,
I'll take it to Clay.
-You've always been
a straight shooter.
[sips, gulps]
Where were you
for the last ten years?
[sips, gulps]
[sighs]
-Sorry about Dutch.
He'll be missed.
-I would be very careful
with her.
-She with Emerson?
-Eh, Emerson's trying
to go legit,
working on a casino deal.
She's making the right
introductions, paving the way.
-What did she want?
-[chuckles]
He's got a new fighter
he wants to showcase.
-Yeah, The Bomber.
He's big,
he hits like a motherfucker.
He's a good wrestler.
I heard some guys
talking about him at the gym.
Look, the other night,
I was out of line.
I just needed to cool down.
-Don't worry about it.
It's all good, okay?
Come on, let's go upstairs.
Talk about these fights.
So the other night,
we just bought ourselves
some time with Emerson.
But the first chance he gets,
you know he's gonna
come down on all of us.
[cork pops]
-So we hit him first?
-Oh, yeah.
[liquor pouring]
But we do it smart.
Keep him happy,
make the payments on time.
In the meantime,
we make our moves.
-What about the fights?
-[sips]
Put them on next week
as scheduled.
We need the cash flow coming in
to keep Emerson off our back.
Fifty grand a month, remember?
You still got your contacts
at the PD?
-I do.
-Want you to find
an old friend of mine.
Mr. Kwan.
He's an information broker.
[paper rips]
He used to move
with some big cats in Chinatown
back in the day.
Did some time
for armed robbery.
Should be able
to track him down.
-You got it.
-Who are you fighting Friday?
-Tank. He's a tough cunt.
-They're all tough cunts, Tommy.
The question is,
can you take him?
-I'll knock out
anybody you put in front of me.
-He's just like his old man.
All right. I'll look over
the rest of the roster.
Make sure we got
some exciting fights to put on.
-So you gonna stick around?
-His father saved my life.
And Clay Emerson
almost ended it.
So yeah,
I'm sticking around.
[mysterious music]
[helicopter blades chopping]
[cheers and whoops]
-Hey. How you doing?
-How you doing?
Good to see you.
How are you doing?
Enjoy the fight, all right?
How's it going?
How you been?
All right?
It's going to be
a good night of fights.
[punch thrown]
-[shouting indistinctly]
-Motherfucker!
-[Bender] Emerson's not here,
just that wack job Doyle.
-Come on.
-[grunts]
[strikes blows]
[knee strikes]
[head slams]
-Tommy's up next.
Tell him to stay cool
when he sees Doyle.
-[Boxer grunts] Yeah!
[body thuds]
[punches thrown]
-[shouts] Yeah!
All right.
[claps]
[audience clamoring]
[muffled intense music]
[muffled thumping]
-[Doyle] Come on, Bomber.
-[Virgil] [softly]
All right. Here we go.
[slaps]
Get your ass in the game.
[punches on locker]
-Lewis, Lewis.
Is he okay?
-[Virgil] Oh, yeah.
-You're up, Tommy.
-[Tommy] How's the crowd?
-Ready for the main event.
-Emerson there?
-No.
But his man Doyle is.
Atlas said keep cool.
All right?
Concentrate on the fight.
[upbeat hype music]
-[man] Let's go, yeah!
[audience cheering continues]
[audience whistling]
[man] You can do it,
motherfucker!
-Ladies and gentlemen!
Get your drinks,
place your bets,
and let's get ready
for the fight of the night!
[audience cheering]
-Let's go!
In the blue corner,
the Asian sensation,
Big Tank!
[audience cheering]
-I'm gonna bury you
tonight, Tommy.
You're a fucking dead man!
-And in the red corner,
the one, the only,
Tommy Masterson!
[upbeat hype music continues]
All right.
You know the drill.
No refs.
No judges.
We don't keep score.
Just one rule.
WIN!
All right, you mutts.
[mic feedbacks]
Give them what they want.
[intense music]
Let's go!
[intense hype music]
[body thuds]
-Not so tough now, motherfucker!
-[man] Get up, you shit.
[punches thrown]
[audience clamoring]
-[man] Come on.
Get up.
Let's go!
[body thuds]
[throws kick]
[neck snaps]
[blood spurts]
[audience cheers and whoops]
-[shrieks]
-[man] Let's go!
-[Doyle] Come on, get up!
[kick thrown]
[body thuds]
[audience cheers and whoops]
-[laughs]
You are one cocky
son of a bitch,
I'll give you that.
-He almost had me a few times.
-Ah! You're the one
still standing.
That's all that matters.
-[Bender] Well done.
All right, Tommy,
let's get you cleaned up.
-[Doyle] Atlas.
What did you think
of The Bomber?
-What do you want me to say?
He's good?
-Well, Clay's going to need
for you to set up
a couple more fights for him.
-All right.
That's what we do.
I'll set him up.
-Well, he wants
to see him fight Tommy.
-Nah. Let's do a few
more fights first.
Build him up a little.
-No. You set it up now
with your rabid dog.
-First of all,
you ever talk to me
like that ever again,
I'll fucking kill you.
Now message boy,
you tell Clay
he's got a problem with me.
Don't take it out on Tommy.
-You think you call the shots?
You're on a tight leash...boy.
[scoffs] Don't you forget it.
[engine revving]
-[Bender] Hey, Ray.
-Bender.
-You have fun tonight?
-Your boy's a stud.
Definitely talented.
-Yeah. You put any money on him?
-You trying to get me
in trouble?
-[chuckles] What an upstanding
citizen like you.
What are we talking about?
I'm not going to get you
in trouble.
-How's everything?
-Same old, same old, brother.
For the, uh,
department of morale fund.
-All right.
You got it.
[engine starting]
-Your guy from the force?
-Yeah, it was Dutch's idea
to put him on payroll.
Kept the heat off us
all these years.
-You trust him?
-He hasn't let me down yet.
-Good. Keep me in the loop.
I want you to go with Tommy
and see my friend in Chinatown.
All right?
Take some of the boys as well.
Let them blow off some steam.
It's been a good night.
-You aren't not coming?
-Not tonight.
[upbeat music]
-Hi. How many guests?
-I think we've got 12 all in.
You should have
a table last name, King.
-Yes, we do.
We got that all ready
for you guys.
-Awesome.
Can you take them to the table?
-Yeah.
-Man, yo,
keep the ladies lit, man.
Keep the party going, man.
Shit, man.
Oh, man.
I can't even [indistinct]
I hope you're talking
about getting my money back.
'Cause you lost the fight
over here.
What are you doing?
Let's go, man.
Get out of here.
I'm not all that easy.
-[Tommy] Yeah, whatever.
I know you from somewhere?
-I don't think so.
-Are you sure?
-I'd remember.
-Uh, is Mr. Kwan around?
Can you take me to him?
-Follow me.
[upbeat, ethereal music]
-[muffled laughter]
[upbeat, ethereal music
continues]
-[Colette] Mr. Kwan,
someone's here to see you.
[muffled upbeat music]
-[Tommy] Atlas King sent me.
-You Dutch's boy?
-Yeah, that's right.
-We did business together.
-[Tommy] Atlas told me that.
Ten grand?
[envelope rustles]
-[straining] Ah.
These are blueprints
for a stash house in Chinatown.
All the details are there.
Kickbacks, bookies, [sighs]
protection money
all go through there.
Triads rotate the location
every month.
[laughs]
But there's only so many,
uh, secure spots they can use.
Eventually, pattern repeats.
At the end of this month,
they'll circle back to that one.
-And where'd you get
all this information?
-[chuckles] You tell Atlas
that I'll get him
with a drop schedule, amount,
and entry points next week.
And I get 10% of the take.
[upbeat hype music]
[clubbers whooping]
[door opens]
-What are you doing in my chair?
-I think you need
better security.
Twenty-five grand.
Half of what's owed to Emerson.
I'll have the rest
at the end of the month.
-Do I need to count it?
-Only if you want to spend
more time with me.
[distant siren blaring]
-You could have called,
you know.
-I didn't know
you wanted to see me.
-You could have called
at least once.
Just a hello or something.
"I'm alive.
Don't worry about me.
I'm sorry I left."
Anything, you know.
I think I deserved it.
-[sighs]
[inhales, exhales]
Wouldn't have changed anything.
[lip smacks]
-Whatever we had,
it expired a long time ago.
-I don't blame you.
Just had to know for sure.
-[light chuckle]
What are you doing here?
-I know Clay shored up money
for the casino
he's trying to build.
-You seem to know a lot.
-[soft chuckle]
He needs capital.
More than the money
he's squeezing from us.
So I got a proposition for him.
It will help him
with his casino.
Clear my debt for good.
-Last time you tangled
with Clay,
he almost killed you.
This time,
he'll finish the job.
-Just set the meeting.
Leave the rest to me.
All right?
You know, eventually,
he'll turn on you as well.
-I know.
I have an exit plan.
Make sure you do too.
[sighs]
[distant clubbers cheering
and whooping]
[upbeat music]
♪ Come and dance with me ♪
-[singing "Butterfly"
by Crazy Town plays]
♪ Come my lady
come-come my lady ♪
♪ You're my butterfly,
sugar baby ♪
♪ Come my lady ♪
♪ Come-come my lady ♪
♪ You're my butterfly,
sugar baby ♪
♪ Come my lady... ♪
-You talk to Kwan?
-Yeah, it's all set.
-Great.
-But for real, yo,
that was a good fight.
But the fights back in the day
was crazy.
I'm talking no rules.
No ropes.
Sucker kicks to the face,
smashed teeth.
Now you guys are fighting
for the crowd.
Back then,
they was fighting for survival.
And Atlas King,
he ruled the ring.
[muffled dramatic music]
-Dude, you saw him fight?
[muffled blow lands]
-I saw him knock a guy out
in ten seconds,
break his jaw,
and still give him his cut
like it was all business.
Heh, cold-blooded. Shit.
I remember when Clay Emerson,
he tried to make Atlas King
take a fall.
He didn't even bend.
And then you know what he did?
He demolished his golden boy
in front of everyone.
[muffled blow lands]
And that's when Clay tried
to take a shot at Atlas King.
He wanted to make
an example out of him.
So Dutch got him out
with a bullet in him.
-How come Dutch and Atlas
didn't just take Clay head-on?
-Clay would erase you.
No name, no nothing.
He would burn
this whole shit down.
No, see. No shit.
-How long you been
sitting on that?
[Eddie sighs]
[upbeat hype music]
-God, Whitney, don't.
Ah! You're killing me!
-[Bender groans]
[laughs] I'll get 'em home.
Do you need a ride?
-No, I'm, uh,
gonna catch you later.
-Um...
Yeah, there's something
I've been wanting
to talk to you about,
and I didn't know
if the time was right
with your dad passing.
But me and Penelope,
I was gonna propose.
Look, I know--I know your dad
never wanted this life for her,
but, um, you know,
I'm gonna get a fresh start,
clean slate.
I just...
I was gonna ask him
for her hand.
-Well, as long as
that's what she wants,
it's her decision.
And Dutch
would have said the same.
Hey, man,
she really cares about you.
[shake hands]
-Thanks, bro.
-Man, cut this lovey-dovey
shit out, man.
We outta here.
-Aight. We'll catch up tomorrow.
-Let's go, man.
-[Bender] All right,
all right, all right.
[upbeat club music]
-Your friends are crazy.
-Yeah, they're
a terrible influence.
-Got a light?
[upbeat club music continues]
[ashtray clinks]
-Tommy.
Never got your name.
-I never gave it.
I've seen you fight.
Such a temper.
-Yeah, it's therapeutic.
-Is that what you tell yourself?
-It's my only playground.
I mean, I'm lucky to have one.
Most people don't even
have their own.
-Where did you hear that?
-I read it in a book.
-Oh, wow!
You read?
-I have my moments.
-Mm.
You on a break?
-My shift just ended.
-You wanna get outta here?
[car honking]
[distant siren wailing]
[distant alarm beeping]
[Tommy groans sleepily]
[distant siren wailing]
[cards rustling]
-[sleepy groan]
-[Tommy]
I didn't mean to wake you.
[lighter flicks]
-[sighs]
You always jump in bed
with strangers?
-Whenever I can.
-[blows smoke]
-Are you a dancer?
-You wanna come?
See me dance?
I'm there every night
before work.
Come by one of these days.
-You gonna tell me your name?
-If I see you again.
-I gotta run.
-[clicks tongue]
I didn't ask you to stay.
[cigarette crackling]
[door closes]
[sighs]
[birds chirping]
-[blows smoke]
[plates clattering gently]
[gate creaks open]
-[Penelope] Hey.
[gate rattling]
I ask you to come at 11,
you come at 12?
-Is that how you talk
to a champ?
-Oh, champ, huh? [chuckles]
A champ who can't figure out
how to get me two baguettes?
That's a ciabatta,
what's the matter with you?
How was the fight?
-[Tommy] I knocked him out.
-Attaboy.
[birds chirping]
I'm worried about you.
-Well, that's part
of the job description.
-Thought you'd be out
of this by now.
Saw what happened to Dad,
I don't want that happening
to you too.
[birds chirping]
-Atlas is gonna meet
with Emerson.
We're gonna find a way
to cut loose once and for all.
I mean, like,
it's coming soon.
-Which is exactly
what Dad used to say.
And he never got out, did he?
The thing he hated most of all
was that he got you involved.
Mom never forgave him for that.
-He never forced me to do
anything I didn't want to.
This was just a hand
that was dealt to us.
-Okay, fine, but he's gone now,
which means it's up to you
to get yourself out.
Before it's too late.
[footsteps approaching]
-[Bender] What'd I miss?
[chair scrapes]
-Uh, lunch.
-Morning, Sleeping Beauty.
-[sighs] What'd you wind up
getting into last night?
-Uh, I ran into that hostess
after you guys took off.
-Nice.
-Oh yeah?
We got somebody new?
-[Tommy] Don't start.
-Sorry,
I'm just asking questions.
Please get your feet off
of my furniture, you animal.
-What you getting into now?
-[Tommy] I'm gonna head
to the gym.
-[sighs]
-Alright. I'll catch up
with you after.
Oh, thank you.
-[Penelope giggles]
-[Bender] Thank you.
[intriguing music]
[train rattling]
[train door hisses]
[pensive music]
-Take her upstairs [indistinct]
[intriguing music]
[door squeaks]
-Hey, what's up?
-[trainer] Go!
One, two.
[upbeat music]
[grunts]
Yeah. Lift your knee
and measure the distance
and strength.
-The knee goes right up.
-[Tommy] Alright.
[panting]
-[Tommy grunting]
-Nice.
Bounce around.
One, two.
[kick lands]
Nice. Be more explosive.
[punching bag thumps]
[panting, grunting]
One, two.
Tommy.
You ready to hit the pads?
Bomber's in the cage, training.
He's fucking good.
Maybe you should get in there
with him and see if he'll roll.
Look, Clay is pushing
for this fight.
Why not? Get in there
and see what he's about.
-No sweat.
[The Bomber grunts]
[kick thrown]
[The Bomber strains]
-They tell me
we're fighting soon.
[kick lands]
[indistinct chatter
in the background]
-I'll put you
to sleep real quick.
-I've heard it before.
Virgil, keep your boy in check.
-What happens outside the venue
is not my problem.
-You wanna go?
-Bring it.
-Ooh, man!
[indistinct chatter]
-[Virgil] Just a friendly roll,
fellas.
No punching.
[door closes]
[indistinct chatter]
-[Virgil] Let's go.
You got this.
[tense music]
[indistinct chatter]
You got this. Come on!
[onlookers clamoring]
-[grunting]
-[man] Let's go, Bomber!
-[man 2]
Hey, what are you doing?
[overlapping grunting]
[onlookers clamoring]
-[Virgil] That's it.
That's it, champ.
You got it.
-[man] Roll him. Roll him!
Just roll him. Like that, yeah.
Back to the triangle.
Yeah!
[onlookers clamoring]
[punches thrown]
-[trainer] No punching!
No fucking punching.
Get your boy, Virgil
-[Virgil] I said no punching,
God damn it!
Get off him!
-[man] Whoa! Whoa! Whoa!
-Fucking do that in the ring,
I'll kill you!
-Cool it!
-He's a tough motherfucker.
But I'll beat him in the ring.
[Virgil scoffs]
-Go get cleaned up.
[exasperated sigh]
[low, pulsing music]
[cigarette crackling]
[distant car honks]
[soft piano music]
[soft piano continues]
-How you doing, Colette?
-You know my name.
-Asked around.
-How long have you been
standing up there?
-Thought about leaving
once or twice.
-I'm gonna go get changed.
-You working tonight?
-It's my night off.
[steamy music]
[moaning]
[panting]
[steamy music fades]
You know,
I asked around about you.
-[Tommy] Yeah, what'd you hear?
[liquor pours]
[glass clinks]
-[Colette] That you're bad news.
And you work for some
really shady people.
-Yeah, sounds about right.
-Do you like what you do?
Beating people up for money?
[gulps]
-Eh, it's a debt I owe.
-Do you ever think
about starting over?
Moving someplace new?
[lighter flicks]
-I have obligations.
-[Colette] Otherwise, you would?
-I don't know.
I never had a choice.
There's people that count on me.
[sighs]
-My stepfather used to play
Russian roulette
when he was drunk.
And he would take his gun,
place a single bullet
in the barrel,
spin it, and put it to his head.
Pull the trigger.
And when he was really drunk,
he would point the gun at me.
Tempt fate.
See if my time had come.
I ran away from home
when I was old enough.
[tender music]
[kissing]
[elevator rattling]
[intense music]
[welding whirring]
-Got to pat you down.
-[shoves] I ain't packing.
[punch thrown]
-[Doyle groans]
-Give me a minute.
I'll be right with you.
-[Doyle coughs]
[indistinct chatter]
-[Clay] All right.
So just make sure [indistinct].
Then we're all good. Clear?
All right, everybody,
give it to me.
My nigga. [claps]
You got the fight set up yet?
-It's on the books.
-Betting a lot of money on it.
-Tommy can take him.
-I don't bet
unless it's a sure thing.
You tell Tommy
to make it look good
before he go down.
Remember,
I'm an old school nigga
with the fast hands up.
[grunts]
You know, all that shit,
the way we used to move.
Yeah! Not all that kicking
and man-hugging
and shit y'all be doing.
[cackles]
And if he pulls the bullshit
that you pulled,
I'ma hang you both up here
by your ball sack, hear me?
Olivia tells me you've been
making your payments on time.
-Just keeping my end
of the deal.
-[laughs]
That's a bad bitch.
Let her slip through your hands.
Ooo, that must have hurt
like a motherfucker.
-Easy come, easy go, right?
-Yeah, that's what I say.
Fuck 'em.
-Yeah.
-[Clay laughs]
-You got a lot of irons
in the fire.
But from where I'm standing,
looks like you're starting
to sweat.
-Yeah.
-I know the feeling
when the walls start closing in.
-It's under control.
She said you got
an offer for me,
so talk or stop wasting my time.
-If you don't come up
with the money
to close on the casino deal,
everything you're working
on here
comes crashing down around you.
-I got this.
-If you did,
you wouldn't be talking to me.
I have an inside track
on the Triad stash house
in Chinatown.
It's a real big fucking score.
But I can't pull it off
with just my men.
I'll need your crew as well.
-What's the take?
-That's the best bit.
Four million dollars.
-Word.
-We split it evenly.
After, me and my crew walk,
all debts paid.
[tense music]
-I'll give you my men
for the stash house job
to confirm everything's legit,
but you want to walk away
free and clear?
The split is 70 me, 30% you,
and whoever else
you got in on it.
Plus the, uh, vig
that Tommy owes on that debt.
Hear me?
-My guys will bring your crew
in on the details.
-My nigga. [laughs]
Now get the fuck out
of my house.
[tense music]
-[Doyle sighs]
-Why did you let him
embarrass you like that?
[knife blade zings]
[ominous music]
[phone ringing]
-[Atlas] It's me.
The other night,
a lot was left unsaid.
-Maybe it's better that way.
-You told me
to have an exit plan.
And that's better
if you come with me.
-You really think he'll let you
get out from under him?
Or are you planning
on disappearing?
-I'll call you when it's time.
[elevator thuds]
[ominous music]
-[sighs]
[traffic noise]
[indistinct chatter]
[children shouting]
-You guys thinking
about having kids?
-Maybe. If Penny wants to, yeah.
-I always thought you should
have a big family.
-I can see that.
Have something to come home
to when you're older.
[children shouting, giggling]
-[Tommy] Isn't that
what it's all about?
What you leave behind?
Otherwise,
we all end up as dust.
[ominous music]
[intriguing music]
[distant siren wailing]
-Is this our guy?
-Yeah.
-What's that?
How much do you think
that's in the bag?
-[Tommy]
It's gotta be 100,000.
-That's a lot
of fucking money, man.
[sighs] And these Triads
don't fuck around.
Fentanyl, jack shacks,
trafficking.
They're gonna be fucking heavy.
This is not gonna
be a cakewalk.
-We can handle it.
[tense music]
-[Atlas King] So we're all set
for tomorrow night.
-[Tommy] Bender got the gear.
Emerson's men will be there
at the warehouse tomorrow.
-We gotta keep an eye on 'em.
And they're bound
to make a move,
especially after we make
the score.
-Yeah. Remember,
this is personal for Clay.
So he's gonna wanna be there
when he decides
to get rid of us.
If that fucker makes a move,
it'll be after
he has the cash.
So stick to the plan
and we'll get through it.
-How's Penelope taking to her?
-Ah, she must have made
a good impression.
I mean, she hasn't been
thrown out yet.
-[soft chuckle]
-The night's still young.
Give it time.
-Hello.
-Hi.
So Penelope tells me
you've never brought
around a girl before.
-Yeah,
we're still trying to figure out
how he tricked you into coming
in the first place.
-All right, that's enough.
-Excuse me.
Why is our guest
doing all the work?
Tommy, would you please
come make yourself useful?
[footsteps receding]
-I'll be back.
[water running]
-Nice girl.
Don't fuck it up.
[utensils clattering]
So Atlas has you all doing
something for Emerson again.
You think there's anything
that goes on around here
I don't know about?
I know you better
than you know you.
-One score.
We settle the debt
and walk away.
-[scoffs] Okay.
Just like Pop used to say,
right?
Last job, last thing,
last favor.
There's always one more
until there isn't.
-Yeah, I hear you.
But we're getting out of this.
And this is everything
we've been working toward.
-[sighs]
Okay.
Then just make sure
you have something left
when it's over, okay?
Someone worth coming home to.
So when you do this--
look at me--
you see this through.
To the end.
[pensive music]
[tense music]
-[Atlas]
The drop's at 3 a.m. tonight,
so that gives us
a 15-minute window
before the armored truck
and the extra guards show up
to move the cash.
There's four guards in the room
with the safe.
One more patrol
in the rear outside.
There's two entrances.
Doyle's team goes in,
knocking on the front door.
We go in through the rear.
Now, we go in strong.
Listen. I'm talking to you.
So keep your fingers off
the trigger unless necessary.
-It goes down how it goes down.
-It goes down
exactly the way I call it.
I'm in charge here.
You do as fucking told.
[gun cocks]
Now gear up.
Me and your dad used to do
quite a few of these.
He'd fucking kill me
if he knew I was taking you
on a job like this.
[chuckles]
-He always said
you did the right thing,
not taking the fall for Clay.
It cost you ten years
of your life,
but you got to keep your pride.
-Now it's our turn
to finish this.
[ominous music]
[ominous music continues]
-[blows smoke]
[chokes]
[suspenseful music]
[door squeaks]
[punch thrown]
[body thuds]
-[speaking in foreign language]
-[speaking in foreign
language][laughing]
-[speaking in foreign language]
[banging on door]
[gun cocks]
[tense music]
[door opens]
[safe lock clicks]
[safe lock thuds, opens]
[tense music]
-Watch the door.
[soft chuckle]
[gunshots]
What the fuck?
-[Doyle laughing]
-What the fuck have you done?
-No loose ends, motherfucker.
Let's go, boys! Let's go!
-[Atlas King] Fuck!
[door opens]
[dramatic music]
-[straining]
[engine revving]
-[panting]
You good? Yeah.
-I told you.
I fucking told you!
You're gonna see.
-Yeah.
[tense music]
-[Bender] We're here.
[gate rattling]
[tense music]
[van door opens]
-Gentlemen,
this is where we part ways.
-No. Plan was to head back
to the warehouse
and split the money.
-That's not what I was told.
We keep the money,
your fuckers walk.
Come on, get the money!
[gun cocks]
-I wouldn't do that.
[dramatic music]
[metal canister hissing]
-[grunts]
[police officer]
Move, move move!
[gunshots]
[police siren blaring]
[helicopter blades chopping]
[automatic rifle firing]
[gunshot]
-[Doyle] Atlas set us up.
Let's go!
[gunshots]
[bullets ricocheting]
-[grunts] Fuck!
I'm going after Doyle.
[gunshots,
bullets ricocheting]
[dramatic music]
[gunshots]
[bullets ricochetting]
[rapid gunshots]
-[groans]
[body thumps]
[helicopter blades chopping]
[police siren blaring]
-[panting]
[laughs]
Oh! You set us up.
-You thought you could
double-cross us?
-Clay will find out.
[gunshot]
[body thuds]
[police siren blaring]
-Not from you.
[gentle acoustic guitar]
[police siren blaring]
-For the paperwork.
-You were never here.
-Thanks, Ray.
[gun cocks]
[lighter flicks]
[fire blazing]
[gentle acoustic guitar]
[explosion blasting]
[ominous music]
[phone ringing]
-My nigga!
Why haven't you come
seen me yet?
-There's too much heat
on the streets right now
after last night's fiasco.
The Triads are looking
for who hit the stash house.
-Uh-huh.
And what happened to my money?
-The police took it.
It's all over the news.
Your men shot
at fucking police officers.
Fucked the whole deal up.
-And yet only my men are dead,
huh?
-[Atlas King] Ain't my problem.
-Word?
You brought this job to me,
did you not?
-[Atlas] And you got too greedy.
Your men double-crossed us
and left us stranded.
That's the only reason
we're not in body bags as well.
If you were anyone else,
you'd be a dead man.
-Oh, is that right? [laughs]
-Word gets around what you
and your crew did.
That becomes fact.
-And yet I'm still owed
my do-re-me.
This doesn't cover your debt
to me.
Not by a long shot, hear me?
-Or your problem breaking ground
on the construction site.
-Oh, you're gonna solve
my problems now?
After you just threatened
to kill me?
-Your men killed the guards
at the stash house.
If the Triads' lookin'
for who did this,
we can't be
at each other's throats.
So let's finish
what we agreed to.
The fight between Tommy
and The Bomber.
-I'm listening.
-The take from that's gonna be
over 600 grand.
The odds are stacked big
on Tommy.
So let the people bet on him
while we bet the other way.
-[laughs]
You're gonna bet on The Bomber?
-I came back to get Tommy
and his family out of debt
and away from you.
If that means selling the crowd
a lie,
so be it.
Pride is what brought us here;
I can't let Tommy
make the same mistake.
-You a cold-ass nigga, Atlas.
I'll be in touch.
[disconnect tone]
[sighs]
-[grunting]
[door opens]
[indistinct chatter]
After the fight tonight,
I'm gonna have to lay low
for a bit.
-Why? Are you in trouble?
-Nothing I can't handle.
But after that,
there are no more obligations.
-What are you getting
yourself into?
-More like what I'm trying
to get away from.
Gonna be my first shot
at a clean slate.
-Oh, yeah?
And what does that look like?
-Take over the fight venue.
Try to make it more legit.
It'd be nice
if you stuck around.
-[indistinct] yeah, grab it.
-Yeah,
I'll catch you guys tonight.
-See you in the fight.
-You feel ready
for the fight tonight?
-Oh, you know it.
What the fuck
are you doing here?
-Emerson wants to see you.
-Yeah, the fight's tonight.
I'll talk to him there.
-Yeah? It's not a request.
-She's got nothing
to do with this.
-Not my decision.
Give me the gun.
Now get in the car,
both of you.
-Don't worry.
I'll take care of this.
[car door opens]
[car engine revving]
[tense music]
-[Atlas] Make sure
you bet it all on Tommy.
-[Bender] I'll take care of it.
-Clay will never see it coming.
-You bringing Olivia with you?
-Oh, yeah.
Don't want to make
the same mistake twice.
-Oh, I hear that, brother.
-Okay, then.
Then we're gonna go straight
to the fight venue.
-Watch yourself.
Watch yourself.
[car door closes]
-Olivia.
Where's Olivia?
-Olivia's not here,
little man.
-Excuse me?
-Emerson would like a word.
[punch thrown]
[grunting]
[kick lands]
-[grunts]
-[Olivia] Atlas.
-What have you done?
We could have gotten out.
-There is no getting out.
I warned you not to
drag me down with you.
-[panting]
What have you told him?
-He knows everything.
I'm sorry to have
to be this way.
But I told you
to have an exit plan.
-I did.
[footsteps receding]
[car door opens]
-Give me the piece.
Real slow.
-We going for a ride?
-That's the idea, Chief.
Don't try anything.
[looming music]
[footsteps approaching]
[Atlas King panting]
-Oh, I'm gonna get the rest
of my money soon enough.
You best believe that.
You thought you could cross me
and get away with it?
[laughs]
You were always reckless, bruh.
That's why Dutch had
to pull your leash.
-What the fuck
is all this, Clay?
This is between you and me.
It always was.
-Leave them out of it.
-You had my men killed.
Stole money that was owed to me.
Put my business deals in danger.
Everyone around you
has something to do
with this now.
Hear me?
-[Atlas] You want someone
to make an example of,
I'm right here.
I'm your man.
The debt was on Dutch and me.
Not Tommy.
-Oh, you my man now, huh?
Tryin' [indistinct]
sophisticated.
[laughs] I ain't buying
that self-sacrifice bullshit.
You and your lap dog here,
you're gonna be dead
by the morning.
Your fight venue
belongs to me now.
-Fuck off!
-Oh, and this bitch?
This bitch here?
I'm gonna have you
turning tricks on the streets
for the rest of your life.
-I'm looking
at a fucking dead man.
-[goon grunts]
-[Colette] Tommy!
-But not you, Tommy.
Rabid dog.
I'm gonna get my satisfaction
with your ass.
Bomber!
Time to play, motherfucker.
[dramatic music]
Show me what you made of, cuz.
-Let's go, Tommy.
-[indistinct]
fucking head off, Tommy.
-[Clay] Let's go, white boy.
-[grunting]
[head smashes]
[punches thrown]
[muffled breathes]
-[Bender] Fucking move, Tommy.
-[Clay] Tommy!
I said I wasn't in no rush.
I'm gonna get my satisfaction,
hear me?
[high-pitched ringing]
-[grunting]
[punches thrown]
[body thuds]
-Yes!
-[Bender] Get up, Tommy.
-[groans]
-Yes! Fuck him up!
-Keep your hands up, Tommy!
-[grunting]
-That's what I'm talking about!
-[spits]
-[laughing]
[Tommy grunting]
[bone crackles]
-Yes!
-Tommy!
-Get up, Tommy.
-[Colette] Tommy!
[punches thrown]
-Kill that motherfucker!
-That's enough, Clay.
-Shut your ass up!
Nobody talking to you!
-[Bomber straining]
-Get out of it, Tommy.
-[Colette shrieks]
-[Atlas King] Tommy, let's go!
-Oh, shit!
[cackles]
[punches thrown]
-[muffled] Tommy.
[punch thrown]
Tommy,
you're Dutch Masterson's son.
You're Dutch Masterson's son.
[muffled] Show this cunt
what you're made of!
Fuck him up!
-[grunting]
[upbeat, tense music]
[overlapping grunting]
[gunshots]
[Colette whimpering]
[overlapping grunting]
[body thumps]
-I'm going after him.
[kick thrown]
[muffled grunting]
-[Colette] Tommy!
-She's got nothing to do
with this.
We have no beef with you.
-[Bender] You got her?
-[Tommy] Got her.
I'm going after Clay.
-Go.
[gun cocks]
[bullets clatter]
[suspenseful music]
[foreboding music]
[dramatic music]
[gunshots]
[bullets ricochetting]
-[groans]
[winces]
[door opens]
[panting]
Oh, shit.
Motherfucker.
[footsteps ascending]
I sure am gonna miss this city.
-Take your last fucking look.
[gun clicks empty]
-Why can't you just go down?
Dutch woulda still been here...
you'd still have had
that nice pieces of ass.
Huh?
-Come on, Clay.
You and I both know...
you were never gonna let me out.
-Who cares?
I'd've taken care of you.
Given you everything you wanted,
man.
All the money you want.
You would've been set
for life, cuz.
-[Atlas]
I chose to live my life.
Make the choices
that I want to make.
-Well, boo fucking hoo.
[punch thrown]
-No, no, no.
No, I've got this Tommy.
I've waited ten fucking years
for this.
Bastard.
Let's see what you got.
Come on, motherfucker.
Come on!
[indistinct] [spits]
I'm gonna fucking enjoy this.
[blow lands]
[laughs]
That's not bad.
All right, let's go.
-Know who you fucking with?
Who you fucking with? [grunts]
Ahh! [grunts]
[groans]
[spits, laughs]
Is that all you got?
You stupid bitch.
[punches thrown]
-[Clay] Fuck you! [cackles]
-Come on.
-Get off me, Tommy!
-That's all you got?
Finish it, motherfucker.
You ain't shit.
[grunts]
[punches thrown]
-He's dead.
[panting]
[pensive music]
[distant siren blaring]
We'll lay low
till things blow over.
-Make sure you get Mr. Kwan
his cut
when you come up for air.
-Will do.
-All right.
-Whatever happened with Olivia?
-She always had an exit plan.
A girl like her,
she's always needed somewhere.
-I will see you
when I see you, brother.
-Yes, you will.
If things go sideways,
give me a call.
-Thank you, Atlas.
-Bye.
[contemplative music]
♪♪